{"data":[{"question":"I _____(ask) him to dinner several times.","a":"have asked","b":"has asked","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the present perfect to say how many times for completed actions\n- I have asked....","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"7"},{"question":"You _____ (not make) a mistake?\nNo, I'm sure I _____","a":"haven't you made\/haven't","b":"have you made\/haven't","c":"haven't you made\/hasn't","answer":"1","explain":"- The question form: Have\/ has + S + past participle...?\n- The negative form: I have + not + past participle","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"I _____ (buy) a new carpet. Come and look at it.","a":"has bought","b":"have bought","c":"have buyed","d":"has buyed","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the present perfect for recent happenings\n- I have bought....","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"5"},{"question":"You _____ (explain) the exercise?\nYes, I _____.","a":"has you explained\/have","b":"have you explained\/have","c":"has you explained\/has","d":"have you explained\/has","answer":"2","explain":"- The question form: Have\/has + S + past participle?\n- I have","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"5"},{"question":"I _____ (not finish) my letter yet.","a":"haven't finished","b":"hasn't finished","answer":"1","explain":"- Negative: I\/we\/you\/they + haven't\/have not + p.p\n- Finish -> finished.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"7"},{"question":"I just _____ (wash) that floor.","a":"have just washed","b":"has just washed","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the present perfect to say that something has happened\n- I just have washed ...","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"7"},{"question":"............You ever _____ (ride) a camel?","a":"has you ever ridden","b":"have you ever ridden","c":"have you ever rided","d":"has you ever rided","answer":"2","explain":"- The question form: Have\/has + S + past participle?\n- Ride -> ridden.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"5"},{"question":"I _____ (not pay) the telephone bill yet.","a":"haven't paid","b":"hasn't paid","answer":"1","explain":"- Negative: I\/we\/you\/they + haven't\/have not + p.p\n- Pay -> paid.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"7"},{"question":"How many bottles the milkman _____ (leave)?\nHe _____ (leave) six.","a":"has the milkman left\/has left","b":"have the milkman left\/have left","answer":"1","explain":"- The question form: Has\/have + S + past participle...?\n- Leave -> left.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"7"},{"question":"He just _____ (go) out.","a":"has just gone","b":"have just gone","c":"has just goed","d":"have just goed","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the present perfect with just for new happenings\n- Go -> gone.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"5"}]}